Hi, I'm Esther and I study at
the University in Frankfort. Hi
my name is Phyllis and I'm a
student at University. Hi, I'm
Abner and I study at home.
Hello. I'm Samuel and I study
in Hi. I'm Vincent and I'm
studying at come Join us on
zoom on November 13th to the
fifteenth for a conference with
students from all over Europe.
Come join us on zoom on
November 13th to fifteenth for
university conference. Students
all over Europe, the topic of
which is the two trees we'll be
covering the topic of the two
trees. We will be covering the
topic of the two trees. I have
participated in several
university conferences
throughout the years both in
the Usa and also in Europe, and
I can testify that I have never
regretted participating. It has
been a very enjoyable weekend
full of truth and life Second
Timothy 222 but flee
youthfulness and Righteousness
Faith love peace with those who
call on the Lord out of a pure
heart uh Deuteronomy 3019 says.
I call heaven and earth to
witness against you. today. I
have set before you life and
death blessing and curse.
therefore choose life that you
and your seed may live. John
Ten BI have come that they may
have life and may have it
abundantly so I would like to
warmly invite you. To come and
join us in this next university
conference can't wait to see
you there